* [](javascript:void(0))[#### Menu](javascript:void(0))

* **Who We Are**
    
* **Plan a Funeral**
    
* **Plan Ahead**
    
* **Resources**

Privacy Policy
==============

_Effective Date of Current Policy: November 7, 2018._

This website ("Site") is provided by Wise Funeral Home through an agreement with Batesville Services, Inc. and its affiliated companies ("we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains how we collect, use, and disclose personal information for services provided on this website ("Site"). Your prior activities on the Site may have been governed by an earlier version of this Policy.

**What We Collect**

**Personal Information.** We collect personal information you choose to provide to us in connection with your activities on the Site, such as using our pre-planning services, subscribing to obituary notifications, and so on. This information may include your name, email and postal address, phone number, and any other information you submit on the Site.

**Other User Information.** In addition, we automatically gather certain other potentially identifying information and store it in log files. This information includes (as applicable) browser type and version, operating system and network, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, whether you are a new or returning visitor, and frequency of visits. We collect and store this information on an individual basis and in aggregate, or combined, form; we do not connect it to an individual user’s personal information.

**Cookies.** A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some of the areas of our Site will be limited. We use both persistent and session cookies. We use cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, to record session information, such as which web pages a user has visited, to enable the Site to remember information about you and your preferences, and to track user activity on our Site.

**Analytics.** To determine how many users visit our Site, how often they visit the Site, and to better understand the areas of greatest interest to our visitors, we use a tool called "Google Analytics" to compile this information for us. As a result of your visit to our Site, Google may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of analytics tools with personally identifiable information. For more information about the analytics company’s ability to use and share information about your visits to this Site, see [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en.](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**Ad Networks.** As you browse our Site, advertising cookies may be placed on your computer to help us understand what products and services you are interested in. When you visit other sites, our display advertising partners let us show you retargeting advertising based on your interaction with our Site, if we choose to do so. In addition, we may show you ads of other companies on our Site, based on your activities on other sites. Our ad partners may collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.

**How We Use Information**

We store and process your personal information in connection with the purposes for which you provided it (for example, to contact you in response to a request for information). We may also send you information about products and services we believe will be of interest to you, and/or contact you regarding such products and services.

We use other information we collect to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to improve the content of our web pages, and to make our Site more useful to visitors.

**How We Share Information**

We may share Personal Information we collect with third parties as reasonably necessary to provide the Site’s services. We may also share your information with trusted third parties so they can provide additional services through our Site. We may share your information to comply with law enforcement requests and judicial proceedings, and to ensure the safety and security of the Site. It is possible that, at some time in the future, our company may be sold along with its assets, or may engage in business transactions in which customer information is one of the assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer.

We do not rent or sell email addresses, postal addresses, or telephone contact information to unaffiliated third parties, except as described above.

**How Long We Keep Information**

We may retain login credentials and entered data indefinitely for technical purposes, market research, and other internal uses. We may retain obituaries, photographs, and remembrances perpetually, both for our own records and for the public to view. We reserve the right to delete information when it is no longer needed for any of the uses discussed in this Policy.

**Correcting Your Information**

You may request access to your Personal Information that we maintain. Send your request to the postal address or email address provided below. To help us process your request, please provide sufficient information to allow us to identify you in our records. We also offer the opportunity to have inaccuracies corrected in all information we maintain about you.

We reserve the right to ask for information verifying your identity prior to disclosing or correcting any information to you. Should we ask for verification, the information you provide to verify your identity will be used only for that purpose, and all copies of this information in our possession will be destroyed when the process is complete.

**Policy Changes**

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Policy. If our information practices do change materially, we will post the changes to our Site and revise our Policy accordingly. In addition, if we have collected personally-identifying information from you, we will notify you and secure your consent before using your personal information in new ways.

**"Do Not Track" Signals**

We do not currently have the capability to recognize "Do Not Track" signals. We adhere to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This Policy applies only to information collected by this Site. From time to time, the Site may link you to other websites ("Linked Sites") that are not owned by us, even though they provide goods or services related to our company. We do not control the collection or use of any information, including personal information, that occurs during your visit to the Linked Sites. Further, we make no representations about the privacy policies or practices of the Linked Sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices.

Be careful of disclosing any of your personally identifiable information when leaving our Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**California Privacy Rights**

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, users who are California residents can request certain information about the sharing of their own personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the past year. The information which you have a right to receive includes the categories of personal information disclosed by us for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and the names of the companies that received such information. You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format, and the information will not be specific to you individually.

California residents can request this disclosure by sending a request to us using the contact information provided below. Please provide sufficient information to allow us to identify you in our records.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you may contact

Batesville Casket Company  
One Batesville Blvd.  
Batesville, Indiana 47006  
Telephone: (812) 934-7500  
Facsimile: (812) 934-1726  
E-Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.wisefuneralhome.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

219 West Sam Rayburn Drive  
P.O. Box 188  
Bonham, TX 75418 Texas 75418

[(903) 583-2161 (903) 583-2161](tel:(903) 583-2161) [\[email protected\]](https://www.wisefuneralhome.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© Copyright 2010 - 24 Wise Funeral Home. All Rights Reserved. | Funeral Home Website by [Batesville®](https://www.batesvilletechnology.com/)
